



BRIAN HAN

I am currently at senior at USC seeking an internship where I can put the web design and development lessons I have learned over the past 4 years to practice. I believe that working for an industry-leading company such as Google will help prepare me for a life-long career in the field.

I have a passion for technology, and find special joy in teaching new skills to those who may at first seem technologically challenged, such as teaching my grandfather how to use G-chat so he could see his cousin in Busan, South Korea for the first time in 40 years. My love of teaching has led to my current job as a T.A. at U.S.C.'s Information Technology Department in the Viterbi School for Engineering, which I am enjoying immensely.

My hobbies include coding in Python, watching (good) scary movies, and practicing my Spanish with my cat and girlfriend (not the same person I swear).



714 900 1650



Brianyhan@gmail.com



References

Patrick Dent

ITP Department @ USC

(213) 821-1400

Robert Parke

ITP Department @ USC

(213) 740-4542

EXPERIENCE

TEACHING ASSISTANT IN ITP DEPARTMENT

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA

Responsible for aiding the instructor during lectures and grading for classes: Advanced Web Publishing, Design for User Experience, and Database Development.

2012 - PRESENT

WEB DEVELOPER

THE ABC'S OF MONEY BY NATALIE PACE

Responsible for creating a financial literacy website with video lessons and games made with HTML5 and Java. The site will be live by May 2013.

2012-PRESENT

CAMPAIGN ORGANIZER

CALIFORNIA FEDERATION OF TEACHERS

Responsible for organizing charter meetings with traditionally inactive local unions. Also was responsible for training new members for phonebanks and canvassing.

2011-2012

PRIVATE AND CLASSROOM TUTOR

HONORS ACADEMY

Responsible for teaching conversational English for ESL students, SAT English, SAT Math, and Beginners' Computer Programming.

2009 - 2011

SKILLS

Website design, wireframing, sitemapping, Zend Code-Igniter, Bootstrap, Sass, LESS, Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Ruby on Rails

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Python, C++, Java, Javascript, Coffeescript, HTML5, XML, CSS₃, PHP, Ruby

LANGUAGES

Persona creation, Information Architecture, Research. Data Modeling, Interaction Frameworks, User Interface Design

UX DESIGN

EDUCATION

BA: HISTORY | WEB APPLICATIONS AND TECHNOLOGIES

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA

Subjects: Design for User Experience, Programming in Python, Database Web Development (PHP), Interactive Web Development (Jquery & Javascript), Advanced Web Publishing, Web Application Project

2010-2013